[Owl hooting]
It's an owl.
I've never seen an owl.
[Owl continues hooting]
Hey, Mr. Owl?
I'm not gonna hurt ya.
Just wanna get a look at ya.
[Imitating owl hooting]
[Hoots]
You gotta be kidding me!
[Grunts, exhales sharply]
[Sighs]
[Grunts]
[Grunting continues]
[Sighs]
[Grunting]
Oh! [Grunting]
Oh, no!
[Grunting]
[Grunting continues]
[Sighs]
[Siren whoops]
[Vehicle door closes]
Hey! I know that face. Gable.
Dawson? You guys got here fast.
No, no, no.
Sergeant Mendez wants to see you.
Your wife said you'd
be here. Listen, uh,
I'm kind of in the
middle of something here.
Yeah, a window. I can see that.
All right, come on.
I'll take you down to the station.
Hey, uh, do me a favor.
Let's just keep this between us, okay?
Oh, absolutely. Absolutely.
[Camera shutter clicking]
? I am not your ordinary guy ?
Hey, babe.
Hey. What happened to your jacket?
Oh. I got into a little
situation at work.
Were you trying to steal candy
out of the vending machine again?
[Clattering]
I wasn't stealing, all right?
That machine wouldn't take my dollar.
Honey, you tipped it over.
I didn't tip it over.
I kept feeding it in there.
And then finally when it did,
the spring released,
and then the Doritos just got stuck
and they were hanging there.
And I shoved it and I broke
the sheet rock behind it.
- That's all.
- I don't... Okay.
Well, they're gonna charge you for that.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
they're just gonna fire me.
- Oh, great.
- Yeah.
Oh, and, uh,
Sergeant Mendez called me and he, uh,
he wants me to go back undercover.
What? You're retired.
I know. But these guys are
close to makin' a bust.
Remember those guys selling
that counterfeit art?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, well,
one of them's been asking about me.
So they need me to make an appearance.
They want the big dog
to bark one more time.
Okay.
So wait, are you thinking
about going back on the force?
No. It's just...
it's one day like jury duty.
Jury duty can go on for months.
Not if you tell them you're a pirate.
You're out in one day.
- Okay.
- Also good news...
It's not gonna affect me
going to Mets Fantasy Camp.
Oh, good. I was worried.
Now you and your friends can
go to Florida and pretend that
Mookie Wilson really wants
to have a catch with you.
Hey, I paid extra for that, okay?
And I don't care if
he's faking it or not.
It's Mookie Wilson.
Bored Mookie is still Mookie, okay?
- Okay.
- Hi, guys.
- Hello, love.
- Hi. Hi.
Chale... whoa!
What is it? Picture day down
at the unemployment office?
Well, actually, I can't get unemployment
because I've never had a job,
so in your face.
He's dressed nice for a meeting, Dad.
This tech start-up wants to recruit him,
and it would be an amazing opportunity.
He'd have a real job
and make great money.
Ah, well,
I don't know if I'm taking it just yet.
No, no, I know. It's
gotta be the right fit.
- Mm-hmm.
- Sure. And, Chale, sweetie,
I think what Kendra's
trying to say for all of us
is you make it fit.
Even if you gotta force it,
you just jam it in there. Yeah.
Wire him up.
Good to see you, Gable.
- Retirement looks good on you.
- [Sighs]
Lot of guys let themselves go.
You're busting my chops, right?
100%. You look like crap.
Hey, Officer Baskin-Robbins,
warm up the hands.
It's like getting felt
up by a dead body.
So what's the deal?
All we gotta do is find the location
of where the deal's going
down and we're good.
Let Cellucci take the lead.
Cellucci?
You didn't tell me
Cellucci's on this case.
'Cause you wouldn't have shown up.
- [Sighs]
- Could be worse.
You could be stuck in
a guard shack window
with your ass hanging out.
Dawson showed you that picture?
Yeah, it's his screensaver.
There he is.
Hey, baby.
Oh.
[Sighs]
- It's been what? A year?
- [Chuckles]
I was starting to think she
traded you in for a new model.
- Oh, no.
- [Laughs]
This one hit the lottery
on the first spin.
[Laughs]
More like a scratch-off when you...
When you win 5 bucks
and you don't cash it in
- 'cause it ain't worth it.
- Oh, yeah.
- But still you won. You did win.
- Not really.
These two, huh?
Anyway,
you guys doing any business in the area?
We have some potential buyers lined up.
Yeah, which is why we were
thinking that maybe...
Domingo, I'm sorry. What is that?
I see the two patties,
but what's in between there?
Is that cheese or an egg?
Both. With two hash browns on top.
- What?
- Yeah.
Um, sweetheart.
Domingo was about to tell us...
Now was that a special
order or did you just...
Did you order that off the menu?
It's the breakfast burger.
It's on the second page.
And the egg doesn't drip on your hands?
Nope, hash brown soaks it right up.
- Wow, that's thought out.
- Okay, all right.
- It's thought out.
- Okay.
Are we done with the burger talk?
Yes, sorry.
Are we done? Okay.
So I'm sorry, please. Continue.
Uh, no problem. Actually, this week...
I'm sorry.
I gotta stop... I gotta stop this.
You know what it is? I just...
I tried to go healthy, but it's just...
it's not workin'.
I'm traveling and stuff.
You know, I'm gonna start Monday.
I'll start Monday.
Hey, waitress? Can I get...
- Honey, honey, honey, honey.
- Huh?
You keep interrupting people,
and they're trying to tell us
where they're going for the weekend.
And I wanna hear all about it,
but I will hear much better
with the breakfast burger.
Two meals, one bun. I'll be locked on.
Okay, excuse me, waitress.
Could you fly in one of
these for my husband?
I'll pay you a million dollars.
Thanks so much. Okay. Sorry.
I like this guy.
You know what it is about him?
He's got an appetite for life.
Yes, life. That's what he's been eating.
So, you were saying where you
were going for the weekend.
Yeah, Boston. We're having
a big art show this weekend.
Oh, Boston.
It's gonna be kind of nice.
I thought maybe...
[Cellphone chiming]
Excuse me.
Oh. Give me one second.
What is it?
I thought you told me it was handled.
I'm sorry. We gotta run. It's business.
- Sorry, it's just...
- No, no. Don't worry.
- But I'll see you guys soon.
- Okay.
- Yes, you got it.
- All right, bye.
- All right.
- What is the matter with you?
What?
I am try...
I'm gonna eat around the bite marks.
No! I am trying to get information,
and you are yapping about your burger!
I'm trying to make things look natural.
- It's called police work.
- [Scoffs]
And what about you?
"Hey, can you tell us where
your crime is going down?
"And if you wouldn't mind,
speak into the tiny microphone
in my blouse. That'd
be super. I like it."
Come on.
- You got problems, you know that?
- Oh, I got problems?
Yeah. [Under breath] I told
you this was a bad idea.
It's a very good idea.
I got us the information we need.
All right,
- you have your own mic, stupid!
- Boston.
- It's Boston.
- Get over.
You know what else I got?
I got two burgers, I got a vanilla malt,
and a salad for my wife.
By the way,
we got a pretty big tab out here,
so if you can run out a debit card.
I scoped out your rezzie,
checked some refs,
noodled around on your app submish,
and I'm just gonna
come out and say it...
I want you here at Nozzler.
Uh, I appreciate that, Parker, but, uh,
- I am an entrepreneur myself...
- [Thud]
and I'm not sure that
I would be comfortable
being a spoke in a wheel.
My dream is to be the wheel.
Hear it, respect it.
In fact, you know who
said the same thing
about six months ago?
Little dreamer named Parker Cohen. Yeah.
And now I'm about to
take this baby public.
Oh, wow. That's amazing.
Yeah.
And that's when we decide to break open
this 50-year-old bottle of scotch.
I don't wanna tell you how much
I paid for it, but I'm gonna.
$27,000.
- Oh, wow.
- That is a lot of money.
Yes, it is.
So here's the offer.
Six figs, stock options,
piece of everything we develop,
plus...
we rent out Six Flags
for our company retreat.
[Exhales]
I do love the log flume.
And here,
a little cinnamon on your breadstick.
A signing bonus.
$10,000?
What do you say, Chale?
Wanna flume to the moon?
Hey, you know where my socks are?
Wow.
That is quite the statement.
Yeah, where, uh, where are my Met socks?
I need 'em for Fantasy Camp.
Why can't you just wear
the socks you have on?
That's a great idea.
So when they divide up teams down there,
they'll be like, "Okay,
uh, we'll take the dude"
"with the eye patch.
You can have the sad guy
with the regular socks."
That's cute that you think socks
are the reason you get picked last.
I've worked for 20
years for this moment.
- I wanna look the part.
- And you will,
but I need your opinion
on something first, okay?
- All right.
- Okay.
Pick my brain.
So I'm about to get
this promotion at work.
Uh-huh.
I know it. Everybody knows it.
But when they make the announcement,
I wanna, like, look surprised
and then humble, you know?
I've been working on it in the mirror.
So just tell me what
you think, all right?
Tell me I got the promotion.
"And the new... whatever the thing is
goes to... Donna Gable."
[Gasps] Wha...
Oh, my G...
- [Gasps] Oh.
- Okay.
Really?
Okay.
You gotta... you gotta
take it down a notch.
Really?
Your eyebrows, they're everything...
They're all over the place.
Okay, but I can't just
stand there like an idiot.
I gotta do something.
Just do what I do. I go from double guns
into prayer hands under the chin.
I do a face bow out into a point.
What's up?
I like that.
Yeah, whatever. Where
are my socks? Come on.
- Ooh, on top of the dryer.
- Oh. Great, thanks.
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Yeah.
[Clicks tongue]
Hmm?
Mm.
[Door closes]
Hey!
Okay, so...
Not a good fit.
Oh. Well, that's okay.
- It was a great fit!
- [Laughs]
Do you see that? What I did there?
Yeah.
Okay. Stock options, a 6-figure salary,
and a signing bonus for $10,000.
- That is unbelievable.
- Right?!
- Mwah!
- Wow. Okay.
So this is amazing,
because I have news, too.
[Chuckles]
I got accepted to my dream school,
Columbia Law.
What?! That's fantastic!
It's way too expensive,
but it is really cool to know
that I got accepted.
No, no. Look, when Nozzler goes public,
money is no longer an issue.
We'll... and this is
gonna be the best part.
Seeing your father's face when
I give him this rent check.
Grab your phone. This is gonna be epic.
Yes! Donna, I got 'em! Awesome!
Mr. Gable, I present to you a rent check
for six months paid in full.
Thank you very much.
- To Fantasy Camp, huh?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Fantasy camp, baby.
- Whoo!
- Going to Mets Camp, are ya?
That's always been a dream of mine.
You know, I played Minor League ball.
I had no idea.
Yeah, yeah.
If you ever showed a little interest
in my personal life,
I probably would've told ya.
Uh, well, hey, have a great trip.
- Hey, Enzo.
- Yeah?
Wait a second.
This was supposed to
have meatball on it.
I just want to make sure.
Yeah, whatever.
You know what I'm talkin' about.
Whoa! Cellucci.
- What are you doing here?
- We gotta see Domingo again.
- What?
- Yes, at his apartment right now.
No, I can't.
We're going to Mets Fantasy Camp.
Oh, now you're just
twisting the knife now.
No, tonight we got the
"Good 'N Plenty Barbecue"
with Doc Gooden and then we
got drinks on the piazza.
Let me guess... With Mike Piazza?
No, Tim Teufel.
Look, this case is on the 1 yard line.
I just need you for one hour. Tops.
One hour, all right?
I'll meet you guys at JFK.
Kyle, grab my luggage.
Hey.
The massage is almost over.
Stella just has to crack my feet.
Gonna be a few minutes.
No problem, Domingo.
If you don't care of
your feet, who will?
- I love my feet.
- [Laughs]
- I'll be back.
- Yeah, good to know.
I like your feet.
[Lowered voice] What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
I got a flight to catch in an hour.
[Lowered voice] Okay. I'm sorry.
Why don't I just waltz in there
and tell a half-naked crime lord,
"Uh, my fake husband has to
get on a plane to Florida
to play grab-ass with
his stupid friends!"?
And some retired Mets.
There's a lot of people down there.
It's big event. It's a big event.
You're unbelievable, you know that?
You worm your way into my case
and now you wanna tell me,
- you wanna tell me...
- Whoa, wait a second.
- Wait a second. Your case?
- Yeah.
Okay... this is my case!
[Scoffs] I didn't worm
my way into anything.
Believe me,
they called me in here because someone
was droppin' the ball. Oh, yeah. You.
- Wow.
- Don't...
- No, no, no, don't you do it.
- Don't "wow"?
- Yeah, don't do... You don't "wow" me.
- Wow.
- You don't "wow" me.
- I "wow" you. I "wow"...
- Oh, you "wow" me?
- Yeah, yeah, I "wow" you.
You "wow" me? Well, listen!
I am this close to solving this case.
Don't screw it up.
Okay, okay,
can you lower your voice, please?
'Cause it is booming!
Shut... up!
The place could be bugged.
[Sighs]
No, look around, dummy.
I am looking. Look with your eyes!
Oh!
- That's how you look.
- Shut up!
Hey, I got it.
- The giraffe.
- Okay...
You don't say "giraffe."
You point to the
giraffe. You point to it.
- You just said it twice.
- Oh, my God! Just...
Check the stupid giraffe.
You said... That's
three times right there.
Okay, okay!
Fine! [Mutters]
Crap!
- Hey.
When did we get there?
Oh, it's just a little
thing I picked up yesterday.
I know you enjoy the
occasional cappuccino
to put a little pep in your step.
Oh, Chale, you shouldn't have.
Those things are so expensive.
But since you did,
let's put some cinnamon
- in this mamma jamma, huh?
- [Chuckles]
Um, hey, babe.
Did you buy this for me?
Oh, uh, I'm not really good with purses.
Is that a good one?
Um, that's a Coach bag.
That's like 400 bucks.
Eh... Mm.
What?
Wow. I've been married 20 years
and I'm walking around with
an Assistant Coach bag.
Ah. I'm not familiar with that brand.
Kevin got it for me at the
Tri County Flea Market.
Um, he got that and my
Alvin Klein luggage.
Whoa. Wait, babe, there's $200 in here.
Huh?
Eh, I just wanted you
to have a good day.
- [Chuckles]
- [Gasps]
I feel like a mob wife.
In a good way.
Oh, Chale, you might wanna
pump the brakes a little bit.
Look, I'm just trying to show everyone
how much I appreciate them.
It's not... oh. I almost forgot.
Jackie!
- Yeah?
- Here's a few slices of cheddar
for you to get that video game.
I am diggin' rich Chale!
[Chale chuckles]
In this house, money buys affection.
Don't hate the player, hate the game.
What the hell did you do?
I barely touched it, all right?
- It was halfway falling off already.
- Well, then fix it!
Okay, let me just get out my
ceramic giraffe repair kit.
I need something sticky.
Give me some gum. Give me some gum.
I don't even think I have any.
Oh, please. You're from Massapequa.
Your name's Vanessa
Cellucci. You got gum.
Come on. Hurry up.
[Chewing rapidly]
What flavor is this?
[Mouth full] Passion bubble.
- Passion bubble? What are you, 12?
- [Groans]
Domingo: Be right out, guys!
Just putting on pants.
Oh, no rush!
- [Lowered voice] Hurry up.
- I'm hurrying.
Okay, give me...
Not enough. Give me
some more. Give me more.
It's not sticky enough. Come on.
Okay, just give me your gum.
Give me... oh, it's so gross.
- Oh, it's like a river in there.
- All right, shut up!
- Hey.
- Thank you so much for waiting.
[Singsongy] Who wants drinks?
Oh, you know what? I think we're good,
because we're in a bit of a time crunch,
so...
All right, well, let's get into it.
This weekend is our
biggest art show in Boston.
We thought maybe we could
do some business there.
We would... We would love that.
Perfect. So it's settled.
You're coming tomorrow. Boston.
Oh, snag. No, no, I mean, I
can't make it this weekend,
- but I think you can, right, hon?
- Yes, I can.
Oh, there you go. It's gonna be great.
And Boston's such an
awesome town, right?
[Boston accent] "Hey, Tommy,
did you touch Bobby's lobster?"
"I did not touch Bobby's lobster.
Bobby touched his own lobster."
[Laughs]
[Normal voice] It's a great city.
No, no, we'll all go together.
We'll make it a couples weekend.
Yes!
Oh, you know, I'd love to, Domingo.
But I gotta throw you a "no can do."
Uh, honey. [Chuckles]
I think the... the doctor can
look at that rash anytime.
Mm. That's not true,
because I called them
and they wouldn't move my appointment.
Mm.
And it's pretty irritating.
- Yeah, he can move the appointment.
- He can't.
- He'll be there.
- I'm not gonna be there
- So I'm not gonna make it.
- He's gonna be there.
- Sorry, I'm not gonna make it.
Sorry. I can't do it. Nope.
Not having you both there would
be a major disappointment.
You know what?
Maybe this isn't the right fit.
All right, you know what?
You won this, my little care bear.
You won this one.
She kicked the table. I saw her...
Why would you do that?
[Cellphone rings]
Oh, come on. Don't do this to me.
I don't wanna know what's
going on down there.
Drinking beers with Mookie Wilson!
Mookie! Ahh! [Laughing]
Oh, come on. That should be me!
Hey, if it makes you feel any better,
I'm having a hell of a time. Enzo!
- Enzo!
- Enzo's down there?!
I taught Mike Piazza
how to make a calzone.
Tomorrow,
he's treating us all to spray tans.
- Except me. [Laughs]
- [Laughter]
- Hey, babe. How you doin'?
- I'm missing everything.
Oh, yeah. But on the bright side,
you get to spend a night in Boston.
You could do your whole...
[Boston accent]
"Did you touch Tommy's lobster?" bit.
I already did it at
Domingo's. It crushed.
I got nothing to look forward to.
I tell you what I'm doing.
I'm going to Wahlburgers.
That's what's happening.
Hey, you know,
it's obvious that they need you
to solve this case.
Okay, that's not true.
Why else would they pull
a guy out of retirement
unless he's essential?
You know...
You know, I do...
I have abilities that a lot
of the other guys, they...
They just don't have, and...
He's useless.
I'm actually the centerpiece
of this whole case.
Maybe we'll get lucky and
he'll get food poisoning.
Hey, maybe I'll even win a medal.
Some kind of like civilian
thing for coming in
at the last minute there.
Yeah, and you know what?
You would deserve it.
He is such a moron.
Donna, you married a good man.
Sometimes I lose sight of that.
Thank you. Thank you.
Mm. Ahh.
- Synced and corrected by martythecrazy -
- www.addic7ed.com -
_